# Paschalis Tsilias

Phone: 698 4767 948 DoB: 26-03-1993

Email: paschalist0@gmail.com

GitHub: @tpaschalis Twitter: @tpaschalis\_



### Personal

Tenacious Physics MSc student with strong analytical skills, a robust technical background, and handson experience on the IT sector. Looking forward to pair my graduate studies with an opportunity on a larger scale of operations, where I can solve challenging problems, cooperate in a team setting and engineer effective solutions on real-world problems.

### Education

MSc Computational Physics, AUTh 2018-2019

Greek Army Mandatory Service 2017

BSc Physics, AUTh 2011-2017

## **Employment**

Research Student Internship, KAIST, South Korea 2016

C++ code, Monte Carlo simulations, Pattern Recognition

The Web Navarinou, Systems Engineer Role 2013 - 2016

Developed data parsing and automation tools, Supported Server and Network Infrastructure Disk Imaging, Workstation Architecture, Lifecycle and Deployment of corporate software

The Web Navarinou, Customer Service 2011-2014

#### **Publications**

Simulation and Track Reconstruction Techniques for the J-PARC muon g-2 experiment – on behalf of J-PARC g-2/EDM collaboration. Sep 2016, XIIth Quark Confinement and the Hadron Spectrum

## **Core Competencies**

Python	Bash	C/C++	Git	Vim
SciPy stack	(NumPy, Pandas, Pyplot)	Matlab	Mathematica	MS Excel
Flask - Django	Apache		SQL	ROOT
Linux Administrator	Data Mining/Parsing	Data Analysis	Advanced Statistics	Visualization